[
{
"ques_no": "1",
"question": "Python was created by ?",
"a": "Prince",
"b": "Sachin Pathak",
"c": "Dennis Ritchine",
"d": "Guido van Rossum",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "2",
"question": "Python is ?",
"a": "Database",
"b": "Programming Language",
"c": "Operating Syster",
"d": "High-level language",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "3",
"question": "To print in python ?",
"a": "echo",
"b": "write",
"c": "cout",
"d": "print()",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "4",
"question": "Python file extension is ?",
"a": ".tex",
"b": ".exe",
"c": ".java",
"d": ".py",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "5",
"question": "Which of these is a loop ?",
"a": "print",
"b": "elif",
"c": "input",
"d": "while",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "6",
"question": "To check equality ?",
"a": "=",
"b": ":=",
"c": "!==",
"d": "==",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "7",
"question": "Which one is a float ?",
"a": "10",
"b": "3.0",
"c": "True",
"d": "3.14",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "8",
"question": "Python is ?",
"a": "Compiled only",
"b": "Interpreted",
"c": "Only for web",
"d": "Machine code",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "9",
"question": "What is type (abc)",
"a": "int",
"b": "float",
"c": "bool",
"d": "str",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "10",
"question": "To exit from loop ?",
"a": "close",
"b": "return",
"c": "stop",
"d": "break",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
}
]